Thurber, John N. Papers 6051
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John N. Thurber Papers
1959-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Thurber, John N.
6051
1.5 cubic feet
1.5 linear ft.
Papers.
5771339
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Thurber, John Newton
5771339
- Lodge 12 Lists of Members, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Lodge 12 LM Relations Bureaus, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Lodge 12 Union Counselling, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Lodge 12 The Labor Angle, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Lodge 12 Roster of Officers (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Lodge 12 Meeting Notices, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Lodge 12 Roster of Committees, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- DLRA Election of Board Member, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Lodge 12 Head Stewards Letters, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Lodge 12 Stewards' Lists, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lodge 12 Merger With Lodge 39, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Merit Promotion-Staffing Plan, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Lodge 12 Constitution and By-Laws, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Lodge 12 - for Dictation, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Lodge 12 Arrears Lists, 1961-1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- AFGE Labor Dept. Lodges, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Lodge 12 Agenda of Meetings, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lodge 12 President's Letters, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Lodge 12 A.F.G.E., 1962-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lodge 12 Budgets, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Lodge 12 Executive Comm. Decisions, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- OPA - Departmental Orientation Announcements, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- AFGE National Per Capita Reports, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- AFGE National Conv. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- AFGE Steering Comm. Member Drive, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- AFGE Thursday Luncheons, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- AFGE District Dept. Institutes, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- AFGE District Dept. Publications (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Lodge 12 Incentive Awards Comm., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Lodge 12 Parking Committees, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Lodge 12 Grievance Procedures, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Lodge 12 Lists of Dropped Members, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Lodge 12 Fun Collective Bargaining, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Lodge 12 Lists of New Employees, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Lodge 12 Mather Building, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Envelopes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- AFGE Misc., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- AFGE's 24th Biennial Conference, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Lodge 12 Membership Drives, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- AFGE, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Lodge 12 Copies of Roberts Letters Misc., 1965-1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Lodge 12 Copies of Roberts Letters Misc., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Lodge 12 For PSI Affiliations, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- AFGE Proposed Const. Amendments, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Lodge 12 Civil Rights Activity, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- AFGE Esther Johnson Correspondence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Upholsterers' Journal 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Record 1914, 1909-1914 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Record, 1889-1897 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Photograph (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  1 Photograph inside